<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Best of the Web on fav10</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Best of the Web on fav10</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 22:28:43 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookies</title>
      <link>/cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:51:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cookies/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:50:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms &amp; Conditions</title>
      <link>/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:49:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/terms/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conact Us</title>
      <link>/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:49:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact-us/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Stock Brokers in the UK</title>
      <link>/top-10-stock-brokers-in-the-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 22:51:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top-10-stock-brokers-in-the-uk/</guid>
      <description>Top 10 Stock Brokers In the UK, April, 2020
 Trading 212 Interactive Brokers Freetrade Revolut Degiro IG Interactive Investor Hargreaves Lansdown eToro Saxo Bank     Trading 212  Markets: US, UK, DE, FR, NL, Commission: Commission Free, Unlimited for all markets ISA: Free Option Trading: No Inactivity Fee: 0 Fractional shares: Yes Pending Orders: Yes Currency conversion fees: None Minimum Deposit: £1 Deposit: Bank Transfer, Card, Google Pay, Apple Pay Withdrawal fee: 0 Trading Platform: Desktop, iOS, Android       Interactive Brokers  Markets: 135 Markets in 31 Countries including US, UK, CA, JP, DE, FR and HK Commission: From $0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 22:28:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-us/</guid>
      <description>Fav10.co.uk compares products and services for you and helps you find the best deals. We do all the heavy lifting for your so that you don’t have to. We present you a top 10 list of hundreds of products and services in an easy to read and comprehend manner so that you can make a quick decision.

How do we compile our list? 
First we find out what products and services are in demand by analyzing news, online search trends and social media posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Running Shoes for Men April 2020</title>
      <link>/10-best-running-shoes-for-men-april-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 03:00:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/10-best-running-shoes-for-men-april-2020/</guid>
      <description>Here is our list of the top to men’s running shoes based on popularity, sales, user reviews and social trends. 
 Nike Air VaporMax Flyknit 3 adidas Ultra Boost 20 Nike Run All Day 2 Under Armour HOVR Phantom RN ASICS GEL-Kayano 360-5 New Balance Fresh Foam 1080 Adidas Lite Racer Reborn New Balance Balance XC 7 PUMA Retaliate Under Armour Charged Rogue 2  
   Nike Air VaporMax Flyknit 3 Air VaporMax dawns a new chapter in Nike innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Best 50 Inch 4k Tv 2020</title>
      <link>/top-10-best-50-inch-4k-tv-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 02:38:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top-10-best-50-inch-4k-tv-2020/</guid>
      <description>This is our list of the best newly released 50-59 inch 4k TVs in 2020 
  Image Model Display Resolution Smart TV Connectivity          LG OLED55GX6LA  55-inch OLED 4K webOS 4 x HDMI, 3 x USB, WiFi, Bluetooth 5.0        Samsung QE55Q90TATXXU  55-inch QLED 4K Tizen 2 x HDMI, 2 x USB, WiFi, Bluetooth 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Pay as You Go Sim Deals April 2020</title>
      <link>/top-10-pay-as-you-go-sim-deals-april-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 02:15:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top-10-pay-as-you-go-sim-deals-april-2020/</guid>
      <description>  Three Classic Pay as you go  3p per minute 2p per SMS 1p per MB No credit expiry period £5 minimump top up       1pMobile  1p per minute 1p per SMS 1p per MB No credit expiry period £10 minimump top up       O2 Classic  3p minute 2p sms 1p MB Expires in 6 months £10 minimump top up       Asda Mobile  600 minutes Unlimited texts 7GB Data Credit never expires but you need to atleast make a call or send a sms to keep connection active £10 top up       Giffgaff £12 Goodybag  unlimited minutes Unlimited texts 10GB Data Credit has no expiry but you need to make a call or text every 6 months £12 top up       EE £15 bundle  unlimited minutes Unlimited texts 8GB Data Expires in 30 days £15 top up       Lebara All In One 3  unlimited minutes 1000 texts 3GB Data Expires in 90 days £10 top up       Three  3000 minutes 3000 texts 1GB Data Expires in 30 days £10 top up       Vodafone  250 minutes unlimited texts 3GB Data Expires in 180 days £10 top up       Tesco  500 minutes 5000 texts 4GB Data Expires in 180 days £10 top up    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Grocery Supermarkes in the UK</title>
      <link>/top-10-grocery-supermarket/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 01:46:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top-10-grocery-supermarket/</guid>
      <description>Grocery supermarkets are in fierce competition with one another to attract customers and increase their market share. They are always trying to lure customers with various offers and promotions. It is a fast changing market and hard to keep up with which companies have the best deals on the market right now, who are offering great quality food and providing the best services.
We have compiled a list of 10 best grocery supermarkets in the UK at the moment based on their market share, customer ratings and social media trends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Tablets April 2020</title>
      <link>/top-10-tablets-april-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 01:38:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top-10-tablets-april-2020/</guid>
      <description>If you are in the market looking to buy a new tablet that has all the latest bells and whistles, and will give you the best bang for buck, you have come to the right place. We have compiled a list of 10 best tablets in the market right now based on sales, expert reviews, user reviews and social media trends.

Here is our list of 10 best tablets to buy in 2020 in the UK</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Budget Android Phones Under £200 in the UK, April, 2020</title>
      <link>/top-10-budget-android-phones-under-200-in-the-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 01:04:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top-10-budget-android-phones-under-200-in-the-uk/</guid>
      <description>It is not an easy task to pick a decent android phone under £200, not because they are scarcity of offers, on the contrary there are too many to choose from and you can easily get lost in the sea of offers. To save you from the despair, we take a look at the best budget phone on the market and compile a list of best android budget phones based on expert reviews, user reviews, social trends and how well they are selling.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>